Charlie Street

17 Temple Street, Oxford. OX4 1JS. $+44\ 7917601977$ ${\tt me@charliestreet.net}$ ${\tt https://ori.ox.ac.uk/people/charlie-street}$

Research

I am a postdoctoral research assistant in the Goal-Oriented Autonomous Long-Lived Systems (GOALS) Lab at the Oxford Robotics Institute, University of Oxford. My current research is focused on the robust continuous-time coordination of multi-robot systems under uncertainty. To achieve this, I apply planning, model checking, and task allocation techniques to continuous-time models of multi-robot behaviour.

Research Interests

- Planning Under Uncertainty
- Multi-Robot Coordination
- Formal Methods for Robotics
- Continuous-Time and Non-Stationary Planning Models

Research Positions

• University of Birmingham

Jan 2023 - Present

2018-2022

- Research Fellow
- Oxford Robotics Institute, University of Oxford July 2022 Dec 2022
 - Postdoctoral Research Assistant in AI for Autonomous Systems

Education

- DPhil in Engineering Science at the University of Oxford
 - Thesis: Multi-Robot Coordination Under Temporal Uncertainty
 - Supervisors: Nick Hawes, Bruno Lacerda, and Manuel Mühlig
 - Thesis Submitted. Date of Viva: 1st September 2022
- MSci in Computer Science at the University of Birmingham 2014-2018
 - Thesis: IntelliJam: An Intelligent Agent for Musical Improvisation
 - Supervisor: Peter Tino
 - Degree Class: First Class with Honours (Average: 92%)
 - Awarded Undergraduate Distinguished Dissertation Prize 2018
 - Awarded Best in Degree Programme 2014/15, 2015/16, 2016/17, and 2017/18
 - Awarded IBM Team Project Prize 2015/16
 - Awarded BCS Prize for Best in Year 2014/15

Projects

• First Fleet	2020-2021
 Deploying Multi-Robot Systems in Agricultural Environments Implemented Multi-Robot Planning System 	
• Team ORIon (RoboCup Competition Team)	2019-2021
 Deploying Service Robots in Domestic Environments Led Team ORIon and Task-Level Planning Sub-Team 	
Supervision	
Fourth Year Projects	
• Alex Rutherford (with Bruno Lacerda and Nick Hawes)	2021-2022
- Topic: Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning with a Model-Based	Simulator
• Yifeng Wei (with Bruno Lacerda)	2020-2021
- Topic: Trial-Based Search for Generalised Stochastic Petri Nets	
• James Wheadon (with Nick Hawes)	2019-2020
- Topic: Multi-Agent Path Finding in Continuous Time	
• Han Zhou (with Bruno Lacerda)	2018-2019
- Topic: Auctioning for Multi-Robot Coordination	
Internships	
• Tom Liu (with Nick Hawes)	2021
- Topic: Generalising Duration Distributions Across Topological M	aps
• Clarissa Costen (with Nick Hawes)	2019
- Topic: Continuous-Time Markov Chains for Shared Autonomy	
Outreach	
• Led Robot Demonstrations at Goodwood Festival of Speed	2021
• Led Robot Demonstration at University Open Day	2019
• Assisted with Robot Demonstration at Blenheim Palace	2019

Publications

- [1] Charlie Street, Bruno Lacerda, Michal Staniaszek, Manuel Mühlig, and Nick Hawes. "Context-Aware Modelling for Multi-Robot Systems Under Uncertainty". In: Proceedings of the 21st International Conference on Autonomous Agents and Multiagent Systems (AAMAS). 2022.
- [2] Charlie Street, Sebastian Pütz, Manuel Mühlig, Nick Hawes, and Bruno Lacerda. "Congestion-Aware Policy Synthesis for Multirobot Systems". In: *IEEE Transactions on Robotics* (2021).
- [3] Charlie Street, Bruno Lacerda, Manuel Mühlig, and Nick Hawes. "Multi-Robot Planning Under Uncertainty with Congestion-Aware Models". In: *Proceedings of the 19th International Conference on Autonomous Agents and Multiagent Systems (AAMAS)*. 2020.

Reviewing

- **Journal Reviewing:** IEEE Transactions on Robotics (T-RO); IEEE Robotics and Automation Leters (RA-L).
- Conference Programme Committee: AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI) 2023; International Conference on Autonomous Agents and Multiagent Systems (AAMAS) 2023; Robotics: Science and Systems (RSS) 2023 (check RSS 2023 is PC not just review).
- Conference Reviewing: AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI) 2020; International Conference on Autonomous Agents and Multiagent Systems (AAMAS) 2020, 2021; International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI) 2019; International Conference on Automated Planning and Scheduling (ICAPS) 2020-2022; Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS) 2020, 2021; IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA) 2020; IEEE/RSJ International Conference on Intelligent Robots and Systems (IROS) 2021-2022; International Conference on Principles of Knowledge Representation and Reasoning (KR) 2021; European Conference on Mobile Robots (ECMR) 2019; Advances in Cognitive Systems 2020.
- Workshop Programme Committee: Workshop on Planning and Robotics (Plan-Rob) @ ICAPS 2023.